# **GOTTARDELLO**

# Valentina

Junior Software Engineer

- 049 3258 402
- valengottardello@hotmail.com
- in linkedin.com/in/valentinagottardello
- github.com/valegottardello

## PROFILE

I am committed to build change that makes a difference. My international experiences and diverse professional background has given me the necessary skills to grow in the field of Software Engineering. Currently open to opportunities in front-end, back-end and full stack development.

# EDUCATION

# GENERAL ASSEMBLY

Computer Software Engineering

Feb 2023 - May 2023

## CODERHOUSE

Web Developer

Oct 2022 - Dec 2022

## NATIONAL UNIVERSITY OF CORDOBA

Associates Degree, Law

Mar 2012 - Dec 2017

# SKILLS

- . HTML, CSS, SASS
- . Javascript
- . React
- . SQL, Postgresql, Firebase
- . Bootstrap
- . Node.js, Express, Ejs.
- . Git, GitHub
- . API Integration
- . Single Page Application
- . Ajax and Axios

# LANGUAGE

- . Spanish
- . English
- . Italian

# EXPERIENCE

## SOFTWARE ENGINEERING PROJECTS

## MOBILIA BUISNESS

- . Static web page of Mobilia Furniture Buissnes
- . Built using HTML, SCC, SASS, Bootstrap

#### TIC TAC TOE

- . Classic game of circle and crosses.
- . Built using HTML, CSS, AOS Library & Javascript

#### TALKER'S

- . CRUD Web application data base backed.
- . HTTP request, handled from server side.
- . Built using Javascript, Express, Ejs, Postgresgl, NPM dependecies.
- . Deployed in Render.

## FIXUP

- . Work space app for a small business.
- . Users can sign in as a business or dependent, manage their availability, clock in/off, see their tasks and check them done. Depends on the position or role in the business can create and asign new tasks.
- . Full stack application., built using React for client side, Express & Postgresql for server side. Deployed in Vercel.

## PLAN MY PLATE

- . Meal plan app with third party API.
- . Users can search and save recipes, create meal plans, and arrange the recipes with a drga and drop weekly plan.
- . Built using React and Firebase. Deployed in Netlify.

## MAP API

- . Single Page Application using its own REST JSON API to display all petrol stations that are inside of the boundaries based on current location, is displayed using the Google Maps API.
- . Team project motivated to handle GitHub instance in a collaborative project.

## MORE EXPERIENCE CUSTOMER SERVICE STAFF

## BARTEDER - Brooklyn Cocktail Bar

Melborune, Australia - Aug 2022 - Feb 2023

- . Participated in the creation of the cocktails menu.
- . I have been able to function in fast-paced and demanding environments.
- . Attention and resolution of problems during and after the service.

## BARTENDER - La Drogheria Cocktail Bar

Turin, Italy - Jun 2021 - Jan 2022

- . I have been trained to provide a high level of customer service, to be able to advise our clients about the high quality of our cocktails and beverages.
- . We have managed in times of increase more than 200 bookings per night.

## GYM MANAGER - Beat Community Fitness

Cordoba, Argentina - Mar 2019 - Jun 2021

- . Collaborated with a work team imparting values of relentlessness and integration.
- . Provided and guaranteed high-level customer service.
- . Obtained an increase in the number of members from 290 to 350 each year, during my period.

## PARALEGAL - Boetto Law Firm

Cordoba, Argentina - Jan 2014 - Jul 2018

- . Participated in the development of a law firm specialising in civil rights.
- . I have handled over approximately 150+ cases, along with more than approximately 100 cases ended in legal agreement per year during my term.
- . I have been in charge of tracking each case and informing the stakeholders about their status.